ANNA REVAN MISAL

Email: annamisal001@gmail.com
7559149795/7559185452
Shikrapur , Pune-413102
DOB:-26th August 1998

OBJECTIVE:

A motivated, results-focused Human Resource professional, seeking an opportunity to utilize expertise, skills, and education to contribute to employer objectives, profitability, and success for a company offering potential for challenge and growth.

An Sr. Executive who is passionate about human resources. With over two year experience in human resources.

Work Experience:

Sr. Executive Human Resources.

LKW Prime Facilites Pvt. Ltd.

Nov 2024 - Present

- Recruitment, Joining and exiting formalities of employee.
- Daily IR, Manpower Reports & Monitoring on Labour
- Updation and Process Attendance Sheet for Payroll.
- Legal Compliance (PF, ESIC, PT, MLWF)
- ESI details generation on Portal.
- UAN Generation & PF Monthly Challan Reconciliation..

HR Admin Assistant.

Piaggio Vehicles Pvt. Ltd.

Jan 2024 - Nov 2024

- Successfully managed the day-to-day operations of a busy office, including organizing and coordinating meetings, filing, and other administrative duties.
- Responsible for scheduling appointments, organizing and coordinating meetings, and managing calendars.
- Managing all administrative function including attendance records, leave records, office management and Upkeep of office complex, controlling absenteeism through dally analyses and motivation.
- Spearheading efforts across developing, managing and monitoring the performance of multi-skilled work Force and ensuring smooth implementation of HR policies for manpower planning, recruitment, appointment, selection and development.
- Entrusted with the task of maintaining data base of all employees, and preparation of various Forms.
- Manage the commercial accounts such as verification of attendance from muster rolls and leaves records and Attendance regularization.
- Handle the entire spectrum of activities across providing facilities support and efficiently handle contraction, house keeping/canteen /garden/pantry services, mail room operations, Record management and house keeping/tea/coffee/water services.
- Acting as one point contact for all administrative matters the Time keeping and attendance, canteen management, guest house management, maintenance, upkeep and repairs of company's assets, Telephone Ines, courier services, procurement, storage and issue of stationery.
- Maintain a flawless communication with the employees, ensure timely resolution of employee grievarices and Harmonious working environment at all levels.

- Maintain the care and use of housekeeping supplies and equipment, etc. Perform regular inspections for sanitation, order, safety and proper performance of assigned duties, inspect storage rooms, utility & janitorial closet, etc, for upkeep and supply control.
- Assure that Housekeeping staff follows established safety regulations in the use of equipment & supplies at all times. Ensure activities in compliance of legislation and regulatory requirements in the department.

Human Resources Associate.

Fiat India Automobiles Private Limited (Tata-Fiat Jv)

Sep 2022 - Dec 2023

Recruitment:

- Hiring of employee as per organization requirement.
- Handling joining & exit formalities of employees.
- Responsible in entire recruitment process starting from issuing a Offer & Appointment letters,
 Relieving letters & Deployments.
- Responding to the internal and external inquiries related to HR.

Time Office Functions:

- Recording, monitoring, and maintaining attendance data of employees.
- Conducting performance appraisal.
- Conducting employee engagement activities.
- Checking & Maintaining of Overtime & late coming reports, Absenteeism Reports etc.
- Assess employee performance and issue disciplinary notices.
- Shift Management.

Payroll Processing:

• Consolidation of Payroll with all inputs like Collection on attendance, leaves, new hires, Separation, employee information changes.

Education Qualification

Examination / Degree	Year of Passing	University / Board	Percentage
MBA	December 2024	Cumbinaia Chill 9 Dunfassianal	Dumaniaa
IVIBA	December 2024	Symbiosis Skill & Professional University , Pune	Pursuing
B.Com	March- 2020	Dr.B.R. Ambedkar	60.00%
		Marathwada University,	
		Aurangabad	
H.S.C	February- 2016	Maharashtra State Board	66.31%
S.S.C	March- 2014	Maharashtra State Board	72.00%

Additional Course:

- Corporate Accounts Manager (CAM)
- Ms-CIT
- SAP-FI Module
- Typing(Eng.30-P/M)

Computer Skills:-		Language Known		
	 MS-Word MS-Excel Power Point Tally Prime STO-HRM 	EnglishHindiMarathi		
Interest/Hobby:- Skills:-				
•	Swimming Travelling	 Teamwork and collaboration Leadership Workaholic and dedicated Agile Creative and self-driven Communication skills 		
Declaration	1:-			
I sincerely declare that all the above information is correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.				
Date :- Place:-		(Anna Misal)		